/* eslint-disable no-unused-vars */
const QUESTIONS = {'200': [{
  'id': 1,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '200',
  'question': 'Which property is used to change the font color of an element:  color, font-color, textcolor, or changetext',
  'answer': 'color'
},
{
  'id': 6,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '200',
  'question': 'The elements that need to be put inside of a form are input, button and:  legend, click, label, submit',
  'answer': 'label'
},
{
  'id': 11,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '200',
  'question': 'Everything in JavaScript is an object: true or false',
  'answer': 'false'
},
{
  'id': 16,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '200',
  'question': 'Git automatically adds new files to the repository: true or false',
  'answer': 'false'
}],
'400':
[{
  'id': 2,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '400',
  'question': 'Which property is used to change the font size of an element:  size, font, font-size',
  'answer': 'font-size'
},
{
  'id': 7,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '400',
  'question': 'What tag defines a cell in a table:  <tc>, <td>, <tr>, <th>',
  'answer': '<td>'
},
{
  'id': 12,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '400',
  'question': 'Local storage data is stored in:  browser session, cloud, database, file system',
  'answer': 'file system'
},
{
  'id': 17,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '400',
  'question': 'What command is used to create to a new branch called name:  git checkout -b name, git newbranch name, git createnew -b name, git branch name ',
  'answer': 'git checkout -b name'
}
], '600':
[{
  'id': 3,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '600',
  'question': 'The outermost component of the CSS â€œbox-method:  border, margin, content, padding',
  'answer': 'margin'
},
{
  'id': 8,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '600',
  'question': 'What element creates a form: <fieldset>, <table>, <form>, <createform>',
  'answer': '<form>'
},
{
  'id': 13,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '600',
  'question': 'JavaScript is a case-sensitive language: true or false',
  'answer': 'true'
},
{
  'id': 18,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '600',
  'question': 'The following command will add all changes to be staged for commit:  git add dontmissanything, git add all, git add everything, git add .',
  'answer': 'git add .'
}
], '800':
[{
  'id': 4,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '800',
  'question': 'If no positioning is set in a CSS element, what is the default positioning:  static, absolute, fixed, relative',
  'answer': 'static'
},
{
  'id': 9,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '800',
  'question': 'The <img> requires a closing </img> to be valid:  true or false',
  'answer': 'false'
},
{
  'id': 14,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '800',
  'question': 'A function __________ loads before any code is executed:  expression, declaration, invocation, return',
  'answer': 'declaration'
},
{
  'id': 19,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '800',
  'question': 'What are the three steps to get changes from the local machine to github:  add push send, save commit push, add commit push, save comment send',
  'answer': 'add commit push'
}
], '1000':
[{
  'id': 5,
  'category': 'CSS',
  'value': '1000',
  'question': 'What is the primary difference between grid and flexbox:  grid is 1 dimensional & flexbox is 2 dimensional, no difference, grid is 2 dimensional & flexbox is 1 dimensional',
  'answer': 'grid is 2 dimensional & flexbox is 1 dimensional'
},
{
  'id': 10,
  'category': 'HTML',
  'value': '1000',
  'question': 'Which best describes the <canvas> element:  placeholder for a form, container for graphics, contains styling for a form',
  'answer': 'container for graphics'
},
{
  'id': 15,
  'category': 'JavaScript',
  'value': '1000',
  'question': 'A function ______ loads only when the interpreter reaches that line of code:  expression, invocation, declaration, return',
  'answer': 'expression'
},
{
  'id': 20,
  'category': 'Git',
  'value': '1000',
  'question': 'To download a Git repository named \'repo\' on your local machine for the first time which Git command would you use:  git push https:github.com/repo, git pull origin main, git clone https:github.com/repo',
  'answer': 'git clone https:github.com/repo'
}
]};
